
let results = [
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Brian May was the guitarist for which band?",
        "correct_answer": "Queen",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Pink Floyd",
            "Rolling Stones",
            "The Doors"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Which of the following is an album by punk rock band Anti-Flag?",
        "correct_answer": "For Blood And Empire",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Infinity On High",
            "21st Century Breakdown",
            "No Pads, No Helmets...Just Balls"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Which former boy-band star released hit solo single &quot;Angels&quot; in 1997?",
        "correct_answer": "Robbie Williams",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Justin Timberlake",
            "Harry Styles",
            "Gary Barlow"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "&quot;Doctor Jones&quot;, &quot;Turn Back Time&quot; and &quot;Barbie Girl&quot; were UK number ones for which Eurodance group?",
        "correct_answer": "Aqua",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Vengaboys",
            "Eiffel 65",
            "Sash!"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Who is the lead singer of Arctic Monkeys?",
        "correct_answer": "Alex Turner",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Jamie Cook",
            "Matt Helders",
            "Nick O&#039;Malley"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Which artist released the 2012 single &quot;Harlem Shake&quot;, which was used in numerous YouTube videos in 2013?",
        "correct_answer": "Baauer",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "RL Grime",
            "NGHTMRE",
            "Flosstradamus"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Which classical composer wrote the &quot;Moonlight Sonata&quot;?",
        "correct_answer": "Ludvig Van Beethoven",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Chief Keef",
            "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart",
            "Johannes Brahms"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Which Disney character sings the song &quot;A Dream is a Wish Your Heart Makes&quot;?",
        "correct_answer": "Cinderella",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Belle",
            "Snow White",
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Which Beatles album does NOT feature any of the band members on it&#039;s cover?",
        "correct_answer": "The Beatles (White Album)",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Rubber Soul",
            "Abbey Road",
            "Magical Mystery Tour"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Kanye West at 2009 VMA&#039;s interrupted which celebrity?",
        "correct_answer": "Taylor Swift",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "MF DOOM",
            "Beyonce",
            "Beck"]
    }
]

// Recibir pregunta
// Recibir respuestas


// Pintar pregunta
// Pintar cada una en un div

